Bruno Buglioni

Full Stack Developer

Spain

https://www.linkedin.com/in/brunobuglioni/?locale=en_US

(+34) 665616244

brunobuglioni43@gmail.com

About Me

I am a Full Stack Web Developer, with experience doing Full Stack projects developed in the PERN stack with React, Redux, PostgreSQL, Express, Node js, HTML, CSS, Express, JavaScript and Sequelize. One of the projects was done as a team using SCRUM with one week sprints.

I have previous experience for more than 10 years as a Dentist, with experience in university teaching, and commercial management. This allowed me to develop skills such as leadership, ability to work in collaborative environments, creativity, expansion of my knowledge and desire for continuous learning.

I am a person with excellent academic background, resilient, which makes me very committed and passionate about what I do, with analytical and creative thinking, actively seeking results and problem solving and excellent teamwork, empathy, curiosity and dedication to what I do.

EXPERIENCE

Full-Stack Teaching Assistant

January 2022 - March 2023

Boot Camp assistant (TA) for Full-Stack Development students.

Main tasks:

- . Coordinate a group of students to achieve integration to the study group.
- . Guide students in the first steps of the course.
- . Assist in the resolution of exercises and promote group collaboration (Pair Programming).
- . Propose ideas for the improvement of the Bootcamp processes.

Henry Bootcamp, Argentina (remoto) - Full Stack Web Developer (Academic) **Proyect: Henry GameOn**

February 2022 - March 2023

- . In charge of the idea and general organization of the project.
- . Team planning and coordination, git flow, jira.
- . Work in the BackEnd team: BDD, models, entities, routes, CRUD, etc.
- . Work in the FrontEnd team developing and implementing the games that integrate the site.
 - . It was developed under the SCRUM methodology using Jira Software as a tool. The versioning system Git and GitFlow. JavaScript
 - . Front: HTML, CSS, React.js, Redux.js, Chakra UI, Cloudinary CDN Service, Third party authentication by Auth0.
 - . Back: Node.js, Express
 - . Database: PostgreSQL and Sequelize

 $. Repository: \underline{https://github.com/brunob43/Henry-PF-Front} \ \& \ \underline{https://github.com/brunob43/Henry-PF-Back} \\$

Individual Proyect: Earth App

January 2022 - February 2023

- . Design and develop an app that provides information about all the countries in the world (obtained from an API), allows combined filters, sorting by different criteria and creating new tourist activities for each country.
 - . Front: HTML, CSS, React.js, Redux.js
 - . Back: Node.js, Express
 - . DBB: PostgreSQL y Sequelize
 - . Repository: https://github.com/brunob43/Pi-Countries

Oh Wear, Córdoba-Argentina - Co-founder

January 2019 - February 2022

- . Co-founder of a textile franchise in the medical industry. Commercial management.
- . Succeeded in installing the brand for the first time in the city of Cordoba through the opening of the franchise that is still in operation today.

Private Dental Clinic, Córdoba-Argentina - Co-founder

March 2011 - February 2022

. Co-founder of a private dental clinic.

University Professor, UNC. Córdoba- Argentina - Teacher

March 2011 - June 2016

- . Teaching of classes in the degree course in Dentistry.
- . Teaching of courses, elaboration of didactic content and scientific publications.

EDUCATION

Henry - Bootcamp Full Stack Developer, Argentina - Full Stack Developer

November de 2022 - March de 2023

Web Development

University of Buenos Aires, Argentina - Prosthetics Specialist Degree

2016 - 2019

School of Dentistry - UBA..

Universidad Nacional de Córdoba, Argentina - Dentist Degree

2005 - 2010

School of Dentistry - UNC.

SKILLS

<u>Tech Skills:</u> JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, React,js, Redux, Node,js, PostgreSQL, Express, Sequelize, Git, Metodologías Ágiles, Scrum, Jira, Trello, Frameworks: Chakra, Bootstrap, Material IU.

Soft Skills: Continuous learning, Creativity, Active listening, Adaptability, Sociability, Communication, Empathy.

LANGUAGES

- Spanish: Native
- English: b2
- Italian: b1